本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：wdjmhs  幸田實果子  香茗小焙
翻譯：丁小七  小花豆  瀟湘月影
時間軸：coco  濤米鬼怪
校對：wdjmhs  面條打包子
后期：寶寶   總監： Wdjmhs
黑白無間道 第一季第六集
墨西哥 科利馬州
洛杉磯以南2721公里
美國邊境檢查站
加利福尼亞州男子監獄
奇諾市
你哥哥的事我很遺憾  岡莫
I'm sorry about your brother, Gnomo.
節哀順變
我也是迫不得已才下手
I took no pleasure in doing what I had to do, eh?
耶穌違背了老大的意志
Jesus disobeyed el Jefe.
他清楚后果
He knew better.
不過還是要感謝你沒讓他受罪  兄弟
Still, thanks for making it painless, homes.
但我不是為這件事找你  老兄
But that's not why I asked you here, carnal.
坊間傳聞說賈維爾要金盆洗手
Word around here is Javier is hanging up the gloves.
可能18個月后就要退出江湖
That he could be out in as little as 18 months.
這事有眉目了
Things are taking shape.
前景很樂觀
It's looking good.
是啊
Yeah.
你們在外邊當然好了
For those of you outside.
但我們這些號子里的人呢
But for those of us inside...
安杰利哥幫退出江湖
Los Angelicos gets out,
我們的保護傘就消失了
our whole system of protection disappears.
毒梟  光頭幫  拜薩幫
Lords, Skins, Bysas...
他們都盼著這一天
they're just waiting for the day.
賈維爾會拿出方案確保你們的安全
Javier has made plans to ensure your protection.
是嗎
Yeah?
那些準備假釋的呢
What about those up for parole?
馬上要刑滿釋放的人呢
The ones getting released soon?
這些情況他都會安排的  蠢貨
He has plans for all of you, ese.
至少  他應該...
Least he could do is...
過來給我們詳細說說
come by, tell us what that is.
我們一直對他很講義氣
We always done right by him.
他也應該對我們講點義氣
He should do right by us, too.
我會跟他說的
I'll talk to him.
味道不錯啊
Smells pretty good.
-需要我幫忙嗎  -你可以...
- How can I help you? - Well, you can, uh...
把袋子里的東西切了
chop up the stuff in that bag.
好的
All right.
我看看
Let's see.
不行  抱歉了
Oh! No. Sorry.
-受不了這味道  -你不喜歡香菜嗎
- Not happening. - You don't like cilantro?
我烹飪的罐燜雞
I make the best pollo encebollado
是格蘭德河[美墨界河]北岸最棒的
this side of the Rio Grande.
過來  相信我
Look. Come here, trust me.
嘗嘗
Try this.
我的天吶
Oh, my God.
味道好極了
That's amazing.
你從哪學來這么棒的廚藝
Where did you learn to cook like this?
我爸爸去世后
Well, after my dad died,
我的一位叔叔...
I had this uncle who...
教了我幾個菜的做法
taught me how to make some dishes
好讓我照顧奶奶
so I could help out my grandma.
我不知道你爸爸去世了
I didn't know that your dad died.
是啊
Yeah.
我那年10歲
I was ten.
有一天放學后
Uh... I was waiting for him to pick me up
等他來學校接我  而他...
one day from school, and he...
沒有來
didn't show up.
我很抱歉  我不知情
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
沒關系的
No, that's okay.
有段時間很艱難
It was rough for a while,
但我和奶奶很幸運
but Grandma and I were lucky.
我們住在一個溫暖的街區
We lived in a very tight-knit community.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我們有街坊相助
We had these neighbors.
他們很照顧我們
They... looked out for us.
特別是照顧我
They looked out for me, in particular.
你還跟他們有聯系嗎
Do you still see them?
-沒有了  -為什么
- No. - How come?
我先是參軍
Uh... joined the Army,
后來當警察
LAPD...
所以就慢慢
Just kind of, uh...
失去聯系了
lost touch, I guess.
但我很想他們
I miss them, though.
我能理解
Yeah, I can imagine.
但我很高興他們當時幫了你
But I'm glad they were there when you needed them.
是啊
Yeah.
我完全理解
I totally understand.
我知道我給警察帶來很多麻煩
You know, I know I dish a lot of crap about cops
但我爸爸外出執行任務的那些夜晚
but... all the nights my dad was out working late,
總有他們部門的人
there was always somebody from his department
過來看我們
coming and checking on us,
確保我們沒事
making sure that we were okay.
也許這就是你當警察的原因
Maybe that's why you became a cop.
為了去看你嗎
Oh, to check in on you?
繼續攪  別燒糊了
Keep stirring. Don't let it burn.
不是  因為你會找到一個家
No. So that you could find a family.
是啊
Yeah.
我根本沒想到
You know, I never realized
反黑組像一個大家庭
how much the GTF would feel like home.
我真的很喜歡他們
I really like those guys, you know?
很喜歡
A lot.
而且...
And, uh...
你自己也不錯  美人
you're not too bad yourself, sexy.
不會糊了吧
Mmm. It's not gonna burn, right?
不會  我把火關了
No, I turned the burners off.
沒問題的
It's all good.
別接啊
No, don't.
等會兒接  等會兒接
It can wait, it can wait.
我感覺你父親在對我們進行監視
I'm starting to think your father has us under surveillance.
我不會感到驚訝的
I wouldn't put it past him.
-什么情況  -不知道
- What's the word? - I don't know.
隊長什么都沒說
Captain's keeping it close to his vest.
你噴古龍水了嗎
Hey, is that cologne?
洛佩茲交桃花運了
Lopez gettin' lucky!
這妞兒是誰啊
Who's the lucky lady, huh?
我可能知道是誰
I think I know who she is.
等等
Wait...
別告訴我是證物科的特里薩
don't tell me it's Theresa from Evidence.
哥們  這妞搞過的警察數都數不過來
Dude, that girl's serviced more cops than a donut shop.
不是吧  特里薩嗎
Ooh. No way. Theresa?
該死的  泰
Ooh, damn, Tae,
-我知道這是什么意思  -你也拜倒在她裙下嗎
- I know what that means. - You, too, huh?
晚上好  女士們
Good evening, ladies.
我們要去...
We're gonna...
誰噴古龍水了
Who's wearing cologne?
是洛佩茲啊
Ah, Lopez.
打擾你約會了吧
We interrupt a date?
沒有  長官
No, sir.
快點  給隊長好好講講你的新妞
Come on, tell the captain all about your new sweetie-pie?
隊長  你要告訴我們來這的目的
Cap, you gonna tell us what we're doing out here,
還是說大家來就是為了嘲笑我的
or is everyone just gonna bust my balls tonight?
我們去阿拉瓦多街和西湖街岔路口的
We're moving on an auto shop
一家汽車修配廠
at Alvarado and Westlake.
有線報稱那里可能是個毒品倉庫
My intel tells me it might be a stash house.
我們要找一輛白色卡車
We're looking for a white truck
被四個人看守
protected by four bodies.
還有兩個街區遠
We're two blocks out.
做好準備
Get ready.
-我們被發現了  -等等
- We've been made. - Hold on.
在那里  就是那輛卡車
There it is. That's the truck.
發現它了
We got 'em.
隊長  你在干什么
Captain, what are you doing?
大家抓穩
Everybody hang on!
隊長  小心
Cap, watch out!
別動
Don't move!
準備  出發
Ready? Let's go.
什么情況
What do we got?
可以去化驗一下  但我感覺味道像玉米餅
We could run it by the lab, but it tastes like tacos to me.
檢查剩余的袋子
Check the rest of the bags.
毒品一定藏在里面
Drugs gotta be in here somewhere.
肯定藏在什么地方
Must be a stash somewhere.
你們這是在浪費時間
You're all wasting your time.
你是說你的情報有誤嗎
You're saying your intel was off?
不  我是說毒品不在車里
No, I'm saying the drugs aren't in the truck,
就是這輛車本身
they are the truck.
檢查涂料
Check the paint.
看看那個光澤
Look at that shine.
是魚鱗
Fishscale.
你是說整輛車都是用可卡因包覆的嗎
You telling me this entire things is coated in cocaine?
幾乎無法察覺的優質魚鱗可卡因
Virtually undetectable high-grade Fishscale cocaine,
沒錯
that's right.
這是安杰利哥幫的車
It's a Los Angelicos truck.
沒錯
Yes, it is.
看看這個
Hey, check this out.
他們是怎么做的
How do they even do this?
他們用來粉刷卡車的涂料
The paint they used to coat the truck with
是由水溶性聚合物和41%的可卡因混合制成的
was 41% cocaine base with a water-soluble polymer.
他們還在分離
They're still separating it,
但看來上面至少有200千克
but it looks like there's at least 200 kilos in there.
看起來你的情報完全正確啊  隊長
Looks like your intel was dead on, cap.
你的線人是誰
Who's your CI?
他很可靠
Well, he's solid.
大家知道這點就行
That's all anybody has to know.
泰  那個司機交待了嗎
Tae, is the driver of that truck talking yet?
一無所獲
Nothing.
我們在商店抓的那個家伙也沒開口
The guys we apprehended at the shop, either.
我們得找到點什么
Well, we have to find something,
任何能證明這些貨與阿科斯塔家有關的線索
anything to tie these drugs to Acosta.
你的線人不能作證嗎
Your CI can't testify?
一名罪犯揭發其他人的證詞
Well, one criminal's word against another
還不足以扳倒
won't be enough to bring down
安杰利哥幫的頭目
the head of the Angelicos.
我們得有確鑿證據使案子無懈可擊
We have to build an airtight case with concrete evidence.
隊長說得對
Captain's right.
魚鱗銷售不會停止
That Fishscale pipeline is not gonna stop
除非我們抓到那個負責人
unless we get to the man in charge of the flow.
每個人都想想有沒有什么辦法
Everyone, see what you can come up
能把阿科斯塔家和咱們查獲的毒品聯系在一起
with to tie Acosta to our seizure.
我去聯系我的線人
I'm gonna check with my CI
確保咱們沒漏掉什么
and make sure we haven't missed anything.
需要后援嗎
Need some backup?
不用  我自己去就行  瑞恩
No, I'm gonna go solo on this, Ryan.
說不定能幫上忙呢
Might be able to help.
你知道我比誰都了解這些拉丁幫派
You know I know these Latin gangs better than anyone.
非常感謝  瑞恩
Well, I appreciate that, Ryan,
但不能暴露這人的身份
but this guy is off the books.
而且鑒于卡特的內務部調查還在進行
And, uh, with Carter's IA investigation still active,
你最好
the last thing you need
別摻和這種事
is this to blow up in your face.
知道了
I get it.
永遠提防我啊  隊長
Always looking out for me, huh, cap?
沒錯  一直都是
That's right. Always am.
究竟發生了什么
What the hell happened out there?
你怎么沒告訴我們有輛卡車進來
Why didn't you tell us they had a truck coming in?
你知道我每周要收到多少貨嗎
Do you know how many shipments I get in each week?
查普爾盯上我們的魚鱗時  你本該警告我的
You're supposed to alert me when Chapel's onto our Fishscale.
我不知道  查普爾沒告訴我們
I didn't know. Chapel didn't tell us.
那家汽修廠甚至不在安杰利哥幫的地盤上
That shop wasn't even in Angelicos territory.
我沒法預料到這件事
There's no way I could've gotten ahead of this.
查普爾是怎么發現
How did Chapel find out
我們的行車路線的
which way our trucks were headed?
他有個線人
He has an informant.
梅塔斯集團的還是安杰利哥幫的
Metas or Angelicos?
還不確定
Not sure yet.
查普爾沒說
Chapel's not saying.
看來有很多查普爾沒說的事
Seems to be a lot Chapel's not saying right now.
你確定他還信任你嗎
Are you sure he still trusts you?
是的
Yes.
他信任我
He trusts me.
只是最近僥幸脫險的次數太多
There's just been a lot of close calls lately
他看你每次都能蒙混過關
and he keeps seeing you slip through each one.
如果查普爾不說
So how we gonna catch this snitch
我們要怎么抓到這個告密者
if Chapel's not talking?
我在處理了
I'm already on it.
今天之前我會有其他消息的
I'll have more news by the end of the day.
瑞恩  如果查普爾不再信任你
Ryan... if Chapel's not trusting you anymore,
我們得把麻煩都解決掉
we need to take care of our problem.
不能動我們隊  賈維爾
My team is off limits, Javier.
你們隊
Your team?
孩子  那你的家人怎么辦
Mijo, what about your family?
查普爾是我的事  好嗎  讓我來解決
Chapel's my problem, all right? Let me handle him.
我能處理好  我知道自己在做什么
I've got it! I know what I'm doing.
讓我做好我的本職工作
Let me do my job.
你必須得抓住這個奸細  瑞恩
You have to catch that rat, Ryan.
我這周還有另一批貨要來
I got another shipment coming in this week.
重量級的貨  有一噸
Heavy weight. A thousand keys.
這批貨我們可丟不起
We can't afford to lose this one.
-那就先運回去  -不行
- Well, then turn it back. - Look, I can't.
現在風頭太緊了
It's too hot right now.
你們查收的那200千克貨  對我們影響很大
The 200 keys you took? It's gonna cost us.
我能還清梅塔斯集團的唯一方法
The only way I can pay back the Metas
就是從更多的貨里賺取利潤
is if I leverage the profits from a bigger shipment.
要是出了差錯怎么辦
What if something else goes wrong?
梅塔斯集團會追殺你
The Metas will come after you.
不  不  他們不會追殺我
No. No, they won't come after me.
在我還清債務前  他們不會殺我的
They're gonna keep me alive until I've paid back the debt.
他們會追殺我們的家人  瑞恩
It's our family they're gonna come after, Ryan.
瑪茜艾拉  丹尼爾
Marciela, Daniel.
孩子  我需要你確保
Son... I need you to make sure
那批貨能安然送達
that shipment comes through,
因為那是我們
'cause that's the only way
保護他們的唯一方法
we are gonna be able to protect them.
你聽懂我的話了嗎
Do you understand me?
你翻我桌子干嘛
What are you doing in my desk?
怎么了  哥們兒
Oh, what's up, man?
我在找上個月
I was looking for that file
你和坦納繳獲海洛因案子的文件
for the heroin bust you and Tanner did last month.
要那個干嘛
What for?
我有個哥們兒
I got a guy
要給我一些阿科斯塔家的情報
who's gonna give me some intel on the Acostas,
但我得還他人情
but I gotta return the favor.
在這兒呢
Here it is.
這是我的文件  我也要去
It's my file. Means I'm coming.
-你開車  -好
- You can roll. - All right.
你這是第二次放杰西卡鴿子了吧
So what, that's the second time you bailed out on Jessica?
第三次
Third.
該死  我知道她生你的氣  哥們兒
Damn, I know she's pissed off at you, man.
她沒事
She's fine.
是啊
Yeah, right.
她不好  哥們兒  相信我  我了解女人
She ain't fine, man, trust me. I know women.
我要是你  我會用甜膩帶有愛意的拉丁嗓音
If I was you, I'd put on that sweet, lover, Latino voice,
胡里奧·伊格萊西亞斯那種風格的
you know, Julio Iglesias style.
打電話給她  跟她道歉
Call her up, apologize,
也許她會跟你銷魂刺激的干一場
maybe you get some wham bam going on.
你怎么知道我沒這么做呢
How do you know I haven't already?
看看你  哥們兒  你太焦慮不安了
Look at you, man. You all tensed up and anxious.
你得好好發泄一下  伙計
That firecracker has not been blowing off, ése.
我們要跟誰交換情報  哥們兒
So who's this guy we're trading intel with, man?
-沃倫探員  -這人是誰
- Agent Warren. - Who this guy?
沃倫探員  是我的好兄弟
Agent Warren, he's a good buddy of mine.
緝毒局特種部門的
DEA Special Ops Division.
特種部
Special Ops?
那是聯邦政府的秘密單位
That's the agency's covert unit.
他們專門收集信息
They specialize in gathering information.
都是些不錯的人  很內行
Good guys. Great at what they do,
但他們的行事作法不合常規
but they're methods are very unconventional.
你是說違反憲法
You mean unconstitutional.
查普爾說我們得找到一些
Chapel said we need to find something
在法庭上指證阿科斯塔的東西
we can use against Acosta in court.
伙計  到現在為止
Look, man, so far,
這條路一直行不通  不是嗎
that has not been working for us, right?
我不知道你怎么樣  我是受夠了
I don't know about you, man, but I'm tired of it.
你好啊  沃倫
What's up, Warren?
你幫我弄到什么了
What you got for me?
不一定  我的檔案呢
Depends. You got my file?
我監聽了幾個梅塔斯幫成員的通話
I got a wiretap on a few of the Metas.
他們沒說什么能用來指證阿科斯塔的話
They haven't said anything to incriminate the Acostas yet,
但我知道他們有一大批貨就要到了
but I can tell you they got a shipment coming in.
-貨運到哪里  -還不確定
- Where's it going to? - Not sure yet.
明天到  而且是很大一批
It's coming in tomorrow and it's a big one.
一千公斤
A thousand keys.
我們需要你監聽的那些人的名字
We need the names of those phones you tapped
以便進一步核實
so we can follow up.
我不會說的
No, you don't.
打獵愉快
Happy hunting.
這才像回事
That's my boy.
你怎么還拉著臉
What's with the long face, ése?
天上掉下個大餡餅  伙計
Christmas just came early, man.
恭喜  一千公斤呢
Feliz Navidad. Thousand kilos.
除非你能查到卸貨的地方
Except that intel you got is worth nothing
否則你的消息一錢不值
unless you figure out where that shipment's going.
也許查普爾的線人能幫上忙
Well, maybe Chapel's informant could help.
我剛剛從線人那里
Just got a tip from my CI
得到了那一千公斤魚鱗的消息  行動吧
on the thousand keys of Fishscale. We gotta move.
緝毒局說貨物明天才運到
The DEA says the shipment's coming tomorrow.
緝毒局錯了
The DEA was wrong.
那批貨已經進入美國了
The shipment already made its way into the U.S.
貨放在城里的一處藏匿窩點
It's being held at a stash house downtown.
-在哪里  -阿拉米達街的教堂
- Where? - The Iglesia de Dios on Alameda.
-一間教堂  -救濟會  完美的偽裝
- A church? - It's a mission. It's the perfect cover.
教堂的負責人皈依上帝前
The guy that runs it has a long history of drug priors
有一大堆毒品案底
before he found God.
如果那里有平民怎么辦
But what if there are people there?
或許我們應該等到晚上
Maybe we should wait till tonight.
那時候東西早就沒了
Stuff will be gone by then.
-只有兩個小時機會  -這情報準嗎
- We got a two-hour window. - How good is the intel?
絕對準
Rock solid.
就是給了我們"魚鱗卡車"情報的那個人
Same guy that gave us the Fishscale truck.
等我們拿到這批貨  掐斷他們的命脈
Well, we get that shipment, break their backs.
就該大獲全勝了  拜拜了  阿科斯塔
And it's game, set, match. Adios, Acosta.
你們一定已經聽說了這次收繳
I'm sure you both heard about the seizure.
當然  全世界都知道了
Yeah, the whole damn world heard about that.
你準備怎么補上這部分損失
How are you going to cover the loss?
這個不需要你關心
That's not something I need you to be involved in.
問題是
But the question is,
為什么瑞恩沒干好他的工作
why the hell wasn't Ryan doing his job?
是嗎  卡洛斯  你幫上什么忙了嗎
Really, Carlos? What-What were you doing to help?
我不是讓你們兩個來吵架的
I didn't ask you here to argue! Huh?!
我們這一周都要格外小心謹慎
We all need to take extra precautions this week.
什么意思
Meaning exactly what?
意思是在我解決麻煩之前
Meaning until I sort out this mess,
你們兩個都要避避風頭
you both need to lay low.
你知道我有多少次因為家里受到威脅
You know how many days of school I missed
或者可能爆發幫派戰爭
because of some threat to the family,
或者和警察有麻煩
or-or-or some potential gang war,
而請假不去學校嗎
or-or problems with the cops?
我已經不在學校了  爸爸
This isn't school anymore, Dad.
我在經營一家銀行  我不能躲出去
I run a bank, I can't afford to hide out.
我可以讓兩個最好的手下跟著你
I can give you two of my best men to watch your backs.
他們會被保護好的
They'll be protected.
丹尼爾
Daniel?
好吧
Fine.
但我不希望他們進我的銀行
But I don't want them in my bank.
他們可以待在外面
They could be outside,
只要盯著大門就可以了
just as long as they got eyes on the door.
好的  就這樣定了
Okay, it's settled then.
你還是沒說你準備怎么補上這部分損失
You still haven't said how you're gonna pay for the losses.
我可能有辦法能補上錢  爸爸
I might have a way to cover those funds, Dad.
不行  我不想再討論這個問題了
No. I'm done talking about that.
你不用擔心  兒子
You won't have to be concerned, son.
你告訴頭目們
You told the captains
這周貨物的目的地了嗎
about where the shipment's headed this week?
已經辦妥了
It's taken care of.
很好
Good.
我和奇諾監獄里的岡莫談過了
I talked to Gnomo up in Chino.
他想知道我們會怎樣安置
He wants to know what the plans are
監獄里的安杰利哥幫成員
for the Angelicos on the inside.
你怎么跟他說的
What did you tell him?
我告訴他這事我們會處理好
I told him they'd be taken care of,
但是他們想聽到你親口保證
but, uh, they want to hear it from you.
我正忙著抓內奸呢
I'm trying to smoke out a rat right now.
沒時間管這個
I don't have time for that.
爸爸  如果你不親自出現
Pop, you don't show face yourself,
岡莫和其他人會認為你不尊重他們
Gnomo and the OG's are gonna take that as an insult for sure.
那就由你去說服他們不要這樣
Then you make sure they don't.
兒子  你去  你去和他們談談
Son, you go, you talk to them.
他們尊重你
They respect you.
好心人  有零錢嗎  有...
Hey, man, y'all got some change? Y'all got...?
泰  小薇  你們繞到后面
Tae, Vee, you go around back,
等我的信號  瑞恩
wait for my signal. Ryan.
里面正在布道
There's a service going on.
不過是阿科斯塔的偽裝的一部分  行動
It's part of Acosta's cover-up. We're moving.
繼續  大家大點聲
Keep going. Let's go higher.
好了  大家注意  我們數到三進去
All right, people, we go in on three.
一  二  三
One, two... three.
別站起來  別站起來
Stay down! Sit down.
女士們先生們  這是場突擊搜捕
Ladies and gentlemen, this is a raid.
請留在原位
Stay in your seats.
我們會盡快結束
We'll get this done with as quickly as possible.
這是什么意思
What's the meaning of this?!
-所有人  坐下  -你們不該來這里
- Everyone, sit down! - You got no business being in here.
我們在做上帝的工作
We're doing the work of God.
我是你現在唯一需要擔心的上帝  帕爾卡
Right now, I'm the only God you have to worry about, Parca.
那已經不是我的名字了
That's not my name anymore.
不再是了
No es más.
你們還是走吧
Why don't you get out of here?
毒品在哪
Where are the drugs?
什么毒品  這里沒有毒品
What drugs? There are no drugs!
把這地方翻個底朝天
Take this place apart!
請大家不要激動
Guys, take it easy.
所有人坐下  保持冷靜
Sit down, everyone. Stay calm.
一小包大麻  你怎么回事  伙計
A dime bag of weed? What's wrong with you, man?
你差點為了這個挨槍子
You could have got shot for that!
房間里沒有
Their rooms are clear,
但后面有一個鎖著的儲藏室
but there's a locked storage room in the back.
鑰匙在哪
Where is the key?
他是我們的牧師  求你了
He's our pastor! Please!
賈維爾·阿科斯塔也是你的教民嗎
Javier Acosta one of your parishioners?
鑰匙在那邊
Look behind there.
好了  帶上他
Bingo. Bring him.
別擔心  一切都好
Hey, don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
兄弟  請你們不要
Hey, brother, please don't.
這里沒有毒品  我發誓
There's no drugs in here, I swear.
別這樣  兄弟  聽我好好說
Come on, brother. Let me talk to you, man.
不要這樣做  別這樣  伙計
You ain't gotta do that, ése. Come on, man.
毒品在哪里
Where are the drugs?!
我告訴你了  沒有毒品
I told you, no drugs.
這都是給無家可歸的人的
This is for the homeless, man.
我們花了六個月時間才搜集到的
It took us six months to collect this.
他們需要這些食物  這是他們的一切
They need this food. That's all they have.
隊長  這地方沒有毒品
Captain, this place is clean, man.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
滾一邊去
The hell you are.
如果你的線人給你假情報
If your CI gave you bad intel on purpose,
說明他可能投敵了
that means he could be compromised.
你去可能正中圈套
You could be going right into an ambush.
好吧  我確實需要后援
All right, I could use the backup.
你說過你不會帶任何人來
You said you weren't gonna bring nobody.
你還說過毒品就在教堂呢
And you said the drugs were at the church!
你和賈維爾設圈套耍我  盧喬
You and Javier set me up, Lucho.
讓我看起來像個傻瓜
Tried to make me look like a fool.
賈維爾說他們要去那里
Javier-Javier said they were headed there,
梅塔斯幫的人要親自送貨
that the Metas wanted to deliver the drugs themselves,
讓我不要管
for me to stay clear.
-可我們有約定  -隊長
- But we... we had a deal! - Captain...
隊長  安杰利哥幫會處理他的
Captain! Los Angelicos are gonna take care of this guy.
賈維爾正在引蛇出洞
I think Javier was trying to smoke out his rat,
給手下人錯誤信息  看是誰泄的密
feeding his men fake intel, seeing who dropped the dime.
我跟你保證賈維爾的人
I guarantee you Javier's men are out there
正等著干掉你呢
looking to kill you right now.
我的人說的沒錯  盧喬  我很確定
If my officer is right, Lucho-- and I'm sure he is--
你現在只是在茍延殘喘
you're living on borrowed time.
好好享受吧  祝你好運
Enjoy that. Good luck.
等等  你不能就這么丟下我
Wait. You can't just leave me here.
你得  你得幫我
You got, you gotta help me.
你對我已經沒用了
You're no use to me anymore.
要是我知道一些東西呢
What if I know something?
通常要出事兒之前
Usually, when something's about to go down...
有人要被逮了或者有突擊搜查
an arrest or a bust...
賈維爾都會警告我們
Javier warns us.
你想說什么
What are you saying?
賈維爾有個內應
Javier has a mole.
你真覺得阿科斯塔在組里安插了人嗎
You really think Acosta has somebody inside the department?
他肯定不是第一個想這么做的
He wouldn't be the first to try.
我不知道
I don't know.
盧喬太想保命  你覺得我們能信他嗎
Lucho's desperate. You think we can trust him?
如果他說的沒錯  我們擔不起這個風險
If he's right, we can't afford not to.
反黑組有67個人
We've got 67 people working in the GTF.
他們每天都跟洛杉磯警局
They're dealing with LAPD,
移民局 調查局還有緝毒局打交道
ICE, FBI, DEA.
我們每天要跟400人聯系
That's 400 people that we talk to on a daily basis.
如果他們中有內奸  一定得找出來
If any one of them is on the take, we gotta find out.
這是基金的年度許可
And there's the annual affirmation for the fund.
很好  現在進展如何
Great. How're we doing?
丹尼  從你投了兩百萬到現在
Well, Danny, since your two mil came in,
我們基金漲了百分之十
our funds have grown ten percent.
那可真
Wow, that's...
-那可真不錯  -我知道
- that's amazing. - I know.
在辦公室他們都叫你幸運星呢
At the office, they're calling you our lucky centavo.
還有機會再投一點嗎
Hey, is-is there still time to invest more?
你想投多少
How much you thinking?
第一筆投資翻一倍
Uh, double my initial investment.
四百萬
Four mil?
對
Yeah.
沒問題
You got it.
太好了
Yes!
你把錢打過來我們再談下一步
You wire over the funds, we'll go from there, huh?
好
Yep.
那周日高爾夫球場見
Hey, I'm gonna see you on the links on Sunday?
當然  我會去
Yeah, yeah, you know it.
到時見
I'll see you.
各位  聽好了
Okay, everybody, listen up.
我需要你們的手機
I need your phones.
把它們交上來
Bring them in.
這是要干什么
What's this all about?
把手機全都拿過來
Right here. Bring them in. Phones.
私人手機也要
Personal phones, too.
看來特里薩今晚得不到補償了
Guess Theresa won't be getting her booty call tonight.
到底是怎么回事  隊長
What's the deal, Captain?
我們可能有內奸
We may have a leak.
反黑組要做一次
The force has initiated
全部門排查
a department-wide sweep to make sure
以確保沒有人的電話被監聽
none of our cell phones are tapped.
技術小組也會來檢查辦公室
We're also bringing in tech teams to check the offices
確保無線設備和電腦里沒有木馬
for wires and the computers for spyware.
小薇  最好把你那些黑人小黃片都刪了
Hey, Vee, you better delete all that chocolate porn you have in there.
你最好把你押的橄欖球隊給刪掉
You better delete your fantasy football team.
真是太不會選隊了
Your picks were embarrassing.
在所有人的設備檢查完畢之前
Until everybody's equipment's been checked,
禁止一切通訊
we will be on a communications lockdown.
也就是說不能打手機或者座機
That means no cell phones, no landlines,
沒有網絡也沒有傳真
no Internet and no fax.
我們還用傳真機嗎
We still have fax?
沒有科技設備我們要怎么追查運毒的事兒
How are we supposed to track this shipment without our tech gear?
用最原始的方式
The old-fashioned way.
人力
In person.
我們可以先去拜訪一下
And we'll start with getting a visit
你那些線人
from your special ops contact.
給你  先生
Sir.
聽著  盧喬
You know, Lucho,
所謂保護線人
this thing about informants is
其實有非常多的限制
they're kept on a short leash.
對他們的保護也取決于抓他們的人
And their protection is at the whim of the people holding them.
我已經把知道的都告訴你了
I already told you everything.
不  你說賈維爾·阿科斯塔可能有內應
No, you didn't. You told me Javier Acosta might have a mole.
可你沒說是誰
You didn't say who it was.
這里是我手下67個人的照片
These are pictures of the 67 people that work in my unit.
我希望你能仔細看一下
I want you to look at these carefully.
告訴我有沒有你眼熟的
Tell me if you recognize any of the faces.
我一個人都不認識
I... I don't know none of them.
我都不知道是不是真的有內應
I don't even know if it's real.
我已經做這行足夠久了
You know, I've been in this game long enough to know
我知道線人都喜歡留點底牌
that informants always save something big in case they need it.
可惜的是
Well, guess what?
警察也一樣
So do cops.
犯人移交書
這是什么
What's this?
自己看
Read it.
"十六起雞奸  二十三起強奸"
"16 counts of sodomy, 23 counts of rape."
你要是不把我想知道的告訴我
You don't give me what I want,
他就會是你兒子的新獄友
that's your son's new cell mate.
請別這樣
Please don't.
你兒子將會經常這么說
Your son's gonna be saying that a lot.
我不知道是誰
I don't know who it is.
我發誓
I swear.
丹尼爾  這是麗莎·布洛迪
Daniel, this is, uh, Lisa Brody.
她是S&C信托公司.的代表
She's a representative from S&C TrustCo.
也是本行的機構貸款人
Our bank's institutional lender.
我知道我沒有預約
So, I know I don't have an appointment,
但我想跟你聊一下你的財務報表
but I wanted to talk to you about your financial statements.
好的  你想進辦公室談嗎
Uh, yeah. You-you want to step in the office?
我還以為審核要半年之后呢
I thought the review wasn't supposed to be for another six months.
沒錯  可是
That's correct, but, you know,
鑒于經濟危機以及數家銀行倒閉
with the crisis and so many banks failing,
我們想增加對較小型銀行的抽查
we just like to check in on our smaller banks every now and then.
有道理
Right.
有一位客戶經理發現
One of our account managers noticed you'd taken
你高倉持有陽光在線對沖基金
a strong position in the SunnyLinks hedge fund.
我們希望盡量能
Well, we were hoping to hold our position
長期持有陽光在線
at SunnyLinks as long as possible.
這對本社區的居民有好處
I mean, it's-it's great for the people in this community.
這種好機會不多見的
You know, we don't get opportunities like that.
可是我們的貸款政策明確指出
But our lender's policy specifically states
資金的百分之八十必須投入穩健股票
that 80% of your money has to be in conservative stocks.
作為貸款方  我們給的條款都有我們的道理
As lenders, we have covenants for a reason.
不僅是在保護我們  也是在保護你
Not just to protect us, but you as well.
我們要求你在本周內
We're gonna need you to move the funds back
將資金回籠
before the end of the week
否則我們可能會強制撤回資金
or we may be forced to pull our backing.
明白了嗎
All right?
當然
Of course.
如您所愿
Whatever you need.
關于魚鱗的運輸有進展嗎
Any news on the Fishscale shipment?
沒有  梅塔斯不討論這事
No. Metas aren't talking about it.
-他們非常謹慎  -那他們都聊些什么
- They're being cautious. - What are they talking about?
除了傻逼的橄欖球
Well, besides the crap about footbol,
還有斗雞和墨西哥摔跤
and cockfighting and Mexican wrestling,
他們還說要事先安排武裝力量
they're talking about putting soldiers in place in case, uh,
以免阿科斯塔的事出問題
things go south with the Acostas.
可他們肯定不會干掉自己最大的分包商
But they won't kill their number one distributer.
那當然
That's for sure.
不  他們會找上他的家人
No. They'll go after his family.
梅塔斯的游戲規則
That's the Metas' playbook.
攻其必救
Hit the Acostas where it hurts.
很好  就讓他們狗咬狗吧
Good. Let the wolves eat the wolves.
沒錯
Exactly.
有消息隨時通知我
I'll let you know if I hear anything.
謝了  沃倫
All right, thanks, Warren.
阿科斯塔的妻兒們
Some of the Acostas' kids, wife,
不該落得如此下場
they don't deserve to get caught up in this.
胡說
The hell they don't.
那家人沒一個是無辜的
Nobody in that family is innocent.
你覺得沒有他老爹的臟錢
You think Daniel could open that bank
丹尼爾能開得了銀行嗎
without his old man's blood money?
你覺得瑪茜艾拉跟了她三十五年
You think Marciela's been with him for 35 years
卻絲毫未享受壓寨夫人的福利嗎
without enjoying the perks of being a kingpin's wife?
所以他們就該去死嗎
So, they deserve to die?
賈維爾一家的下場如何
It-it's not my job to worry about
跟我沒有任何關系
what happens to Javier's family.
我的職責是抓到他運毒
It's job to bust his shipment.
我跟你說件事  隊長
Well, I tell you one thing, Captain.
除非梅塔斯的人再談起他們的運貨路線
Unless these Metas start talking about their routes again,
我們什么都抓不到
we ain't gonna be busting nothing.
我知道  我有個法子能解決這個問題
I know. I think I got a way to make that happen.
我有些消息
I got some news.
他們突襲了林蔭大道上的教堂
They busted the church on Alameda.
你給條子放假消息揪出內奸這招奏效了
Your idea to smoke out the rat by feeding our captains fake intel worked.
所以  盧喬就是內奸嗎
So, Lucho's my rat?
他在哪兒
Where is he?
我想親手解決他
I want to take care of him myself.
對不起  老大
Sorry, boss.
我們到處都找了
We searched everywhere.
看來那哥們跑路了
It looks like the vato's gone.
你問過瑞恩嗎
You ask Ryan?
他沒接電話
He's still not answering.
但樓下有人找你
But you have a visitor downstairs.
讓他等著
Tell him to wait.
我覺得你想見這個人
I think you might want to see this.
你收藏的威士忌真不錯啊
You have a great selection of scotch here.
糟糕的一天過后
This is a nice place to
這是個好地方來放松一下
unwind at the end of a hard day.
我對教堂的事深表遺憾  查普爾
Sorry about what happened at the church, Chapel.
我希望這不會太讓你難堪
I hope it doesn't cause you too much embarrassment.
沒錯  我得
Yeah, I got,
我得恭喜你
I got to hand it to you.
用教堂來試探  這招不錯
The church was a nice touch.
我還以為你會感激我
Thought you'd appreciate that.
為了讓你不再自取其辱  我跟你直說吧
Allow me to save you from further humiliation by telling you,
你的線人盧喬知之甚少  沒法幫你了
your informant Lucho doesn't know anything more that can help you.
對我來說  好消息是安杰利哥幫愿意幫忙的
Well, the good news for me is he's not the only Angelico
不只他一個
who's willing to talk.
正和你意  對吧
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
我們都心知肚明你的線人只有一個
We both know you don't have another informant.
你知道
You do know
你最信任的那個人
that the people you trust the most
會是最終抓你的那個人  對吧
are the ones who get you in end, don't you?
你到底來干嘛
Why are you here?
出于職業道德  賈維爾
Professional courtesy, Javier.
我覺得二十年過去了
I thought after 20 years,
我至少也該給你一個做好事的機會
the least I could do is give you the opportunity to do the right thing.
真的嗎
Really?
那是什么
What's that?
保護好你的家庭
Protect your family.
我絕對有能力保護好我的家庭
I'm more than capable of doing that on my own.
不會了
But you won't be.
明天早晨等我收繳了你那一噸貨
Not after I bust the thousand keys
你就沒法再保護你的家庭了
you have coming in tomorrow morning.
你得逞不了的  查普爾
That another White Whale, Chapel?
這次不是了
Not this time.
我知道等你付不出錢時
See, I know what the Metas will do
梅塔斯一定會對你家人下手
to your family when you can't pay.
你現在就自首
You turn yourself in right now,
我讓你全家加入證人保護計劃
I'll put them all in Witness Protection.
我對你保證
You have my word on that.
問題是  查普爾
The problem, Chapel,
我知道你的保證意味著什么
is I know what your word means.
狗屁不是
Nothing.
跟你的情報一樣
Just like your intel.
看來我們只能拭目以待了
I guess we'll just have to wait and see, won't we?
你知道莫比·迪克最后怎么樣了吧
You know what happened at the end of Moby Dick, right?
那只白鯨嗎
The whale?
它殺了所有人
He killed everyone.
你覺得他在虛張聲勢嗎
You think he's bluffing?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我們不能冒險
But we can't take any chances.
給梅塔斯發條編碼信息
Send a coded message to the Metas.
我們得重新規劃運貨路線
We got to reroute the shipment.
我不知道你昨晚干了什么  但它奏效了
I don't know what you did last night, Captain, but it worked.
沃倫說他又聯絡梅塔斯了
Warren said the Metas are communicating again.
很好  他們說了什么
Good, what are they saying?
他們沒在說話  他們在放歌
They're not saying, they're singing.
一遍遍地重復播放這首梅倫格舞曲
Keep playing this merengue crap over and over.
這是個編碼  他們知道我們在竊聽
It's a code. They know we're listening.
這個詞是什么意思嗎
What does that mean-- Tiburón?
鯊魚
It means "Shark."
或許代表著船
Maybe it's a boat.
上次我們抓到他們陸運
I mean, last time we busted their trucks,
所以現在他們海運貨物了
so now they're moving the shipment by sea.
瑪麗安德爾灣里有個鯊魚碼頭
There's a Tiburón Pier in Marina del Rey.
等等
Now, hold on.
他們放了兩遍
They're playing the song twice,
每遍暫停的時間點都不同
and stopping it a different place each time.
這是個序列  聽著
It's a sequence, look.
第一次暫停是在33秒時
First time they stop it at 33,
然后是44秒
then 44,
3分42秒
3:42.
第二遍在1分18秒和1分54秒暫停
The second time it's at 1:18 and 1:54.
或許這是船只注冊號
Maybe it's boat registration numbers.
不對  注冊號的位數沒那么多
No, that's too many numbers.
他們要進如此大量的貨
Maybe they're bringing in two boats.
或許是要用兩艘船運
A shipment that big.
十三位數
13 numbers.
可能是坐標
Could be coordinates.
膜拜哥吧
Choke my chicken, man.
-什么  -找到了
- What? - That's our location.
新港紐斯船塢
Newport Shipyard.
這是個修船廠
It's a repair yard.
船只過往稀少
Very little traffic.
完美地點
It's perfect.
準備行動
Let's gear up.
至少有十二個全副武裝的
We're expecting at least a dozen heavily armed
安杰利哥幫打手在護送這批貨
Angelico soldiers guarding this shipment.
我們得全力以赴
We need to be on our A-game, people.
他們發現我們了  小心點
They've spotted us! Be careful!
警員中槍
Officer down!
有警察受傷
干掉他們  拿到那批貨
Take them out! Get that shipment!
這些是安杰利哥幫的打手
Those are Los Angelico soldiers.
我發現六個
I count six!
芭芭拉號
瑪麗安德爾灣
他們在燒毀毒品
They're burning the drugs!
泰  小薇  掩護我們  我們得趕快移動了
Tae, Vee, give us some cover. We're gonna move.
洛佩茲
Lopez!
洛佩茲去哪兒了
Where the hell is Lopez?
走  快走
Go! Just go!
別開槍
別開槍  住手
你得馬上沉船
-我沒看到毒品  -洛佩茲  報告你的位置
- I don't see the drugs. - Lopez, what's your 20?
洛佩茲  再說一遍  報告你的位置
Lopez, repeat, what's your 20?
我看到你跑過去  怎么了
I saw you running over here. What happened?
他們想要沉船
They were trying to sink the sub!
幫我關閘
Help me close the vents.
我的天吶
I'll be damned.
找到了
We got it.
是啊
Yeah.
卡洛斯
Hey, Carlos!
兄弟
Orale, carnal.
卡洛斯
Carlos.
這個月的錢
This month's package.
謝謝
Gracias.
我還以為會是你父親來
I thought your father was coming.
我父親讓我轉達
My father asked me to relay a message.
所有的兄弟  退休的和終身監禁的
All the homeys, the OGs and the lifers,
幫里會照顧好你們
they're all gonna be taken care of.
只要還有一個安杰利哥幫成員被關在這兒
As long as there's a single Angelico locked up in here,
我父親就會繼續交保護費
my father will continue to pay the fees
保證你們的安全
to insure your protection.
那些出獄的會怎么樣
What about those of us getting out?
他們嗎
What about them?
他們可以像我們其他人一樣混白道
They can go straight like the rest of us, eh?
我父親買下了幾家餐館和幾棟公寓
My father's buying restaurants and apartment buildings
可以給他們提供很多工作崗位
so there will be plenty of J-O-Bs for them.
比如清潔工  服務生
Like janitors, waiters
這類的活計嗎
and things like that?
總得先起步  再一步步往上爬
Hey, you got to start somewhere then work your way up.
你懂什么
Tú no sabes qué?
我已經是高層了  伙計
I'm already up, homes.
我一出獄  就要回幫里
Soon as I get out, I'm gonna go back to the hood,
賣毒品  每天賺大錢
sling dope, make a grand a day.
我也想走正道
I'm all for going legit,
但我有三個孩子
but I got three kids.
拿最低工資怎么糊口
I can't live on no minimum wage.
你知道嗎
Y sabes qué?
這兒的大多數人都不行
Most of the homeys in here can't either.
好吧  放心  岡莫
All right, easy, Gnomo.
你會有很多生活費
You'll have plenty of cash to live on.
我保證照顧好你
I'll make sure you're taken care of.
就像你照顧我弟弟一樣嗎
Like you took care of my brother?
你想說什么  蠢貨
Something you want to say, ese?
你知道
You know,
你父親至少要做到
the least your father could have done
尊重我們  當面跟我們說
is had the respect to come tell this to our face.
但他不尊重我們
But he doesn't respect us,
他也不尊重你  伙計
and he doesn't respect you, homes.
看看你
I mean, look at you, ese.
你有什么實力
You running a clica of what?
就20個人
20 guys?
如果你父親信任你
If your father believed in you,
他會讓你管理街區
it would be you running the streets,
而不是戈多
not Tio Gordo.
賈維爾洗白后會怎樣
And what happens when Javier gets out?
你真以為在你老爸的新世界里
Do you really think in his new world order
他會讓你管事嗎
your daddy is gonna let you run his spreadsheets?
不會的  到時候就是丹尼爾掌權了
Nah, homes, it's gonna be Daniel in charge.
幫我個忙  伙計
So do me a favor, homes,
別告訴我你一絲油水都撈不到
don't tell me you're gonna be taking care of nothing.
但你想想  岡莫
Yeah, but check this out, Gnomo.
家族要洗白了
The family is going... legit.
無論你愿不愿意
Whether you like it or not.
你要么就抓住
So you can either take the opportunity
我們好心給你的機會
that we are most so kindly handing to you,
要么你就自力更生吧
or you can take a dive all on your own, ese.
你自己選
That's your call.
去死吧  伙計
Well, screw that, homes.
我寧愿在地獄當老大  也不愿去天堂跑腿
I'd rather rule in hell than serve in heaven.
你我都知道  你也是這樣
And we both know you would, too.
是嗎
Yeah?
無論如何
Whether that's true or not,
這是未來趨勢
the future's coming,
你我都無力阻止
and there ain't nothing you and me can do about it.
你聽說過36法案嗎
Hey, did you hear about Prop 36? Hmm?
他們會允許大部分三進宮的犯人保釋
They're gonna be letting most of the three strikers out.
下個月有至少幾百人要出獄
That's at least a couple of hundred of us in the next month.
小心點  岡莫
Cuidado, Gnomo.
你在威脅我嗎
You threatening me?
不
Nah, homes.
我是說  如果你父親想洗白
All I'm saying is if your father wants to go legit,
隨便他
let him.
但我們不用洗白
But we don't have to.
我們只需要一個新領袖
All we need is a new leader to hold the keys.
還有我的錢  和他們的
And my money and theirs,
我們的錢都指望你了  卡洛斯
our money is on you, Carlos.
這是反黑組兩天內展開的
This is the second major drug bust
第二次大規模緝毒活動
for the Gang Task Force in just under 48 hours.
繳獲的魚鱗海洛因總量
The total amount of Fishscale cocaine seized,
高達2600磅
a whopping 2,600 pounds.
總價值超過一億兩千萬
The street value, over $120 million.
查普爾隊長  此次行動大獲成功
Captain Chapel, this is such a momentous win.
你感覺如何
How do you feel?
我感覺如何
How do I feel?
我損失了兩個優秀的手下
I feel like I lost two good men today,
但我為反黑組感到驕傲
but I'm proud of the GTF team.
是他們  他們是勇氣
It's them, it's their courage
才能繳獲如此大量的毒品
that makes seizures like this possible.
你找到了潛艇  好樣的
Hey, nice catch on that sub.
謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
有件事我沒搞懂
There's just one thing I don't get.
那艘船著火的時候  你卻跑向了另一邊
When that boat started to burn, you ran the other way.
我感覺不對勁
Something didn't feel right.
感覺像是聲東擊西
It felt like it was a diversion or something.
我看過去  發現了潛艇
I looked over and, uh, caught a glimpse of the sub.
趕在他們沉船前跑了過去
Ran before they could scuttle it.
卡修斯在無線電上找你
Cassius hit you on the two-way.
你怎么不回話
Why didn't you just radio him back?
我在跟人交火呢
I was taking fire, hauling ass.
沒時間
Didn't have any time.
總之  今天真是大獲成功
Anyway, man, that was a huge bust today.
一切就這么發生了
I mean, when things come together like this,
這感覺真是太棒了  不是嗎
it's the best feeling in the world, isn't it?
是啊
Yeah, totally.
好樣的  伙計
Good stuff out there, man.
第二次大規模緝毒活動
...Gang Task Force in just under 48 hours.
繳獲的魚鱗海洛因總量...
The total amount of... Yeah.
我這就去  老兄  別擔心
I'm on my way, Tio. Don't worry.
高達2600磅
...a whopping 2,600 pounds.
總價值...
The street value...
伙計  謝謝你能來
Hey, man. Thanks for coming. Hey.
開玩笑  我當然會來
You kidding me? Of course I came.
怎么了  丹尼
What's going on, Danny?
你剛剛投資基金
Look, you just wired over the funds.
-現在突然又想撤資了嗎  -我知道
- Now you suddenly want to disinvest them? - I know.
-抱歉  -今年的回報率那么高
- I'm sorry. - We're having our best year yet.
杰森  我也不想這樣
Look, Jason, I don't want to do this, okay?
但貸方威脅說  如果不這樣
But my lender's threatening to pull the money
他就把錢從銀行撤出來
out of the bank if I don't.
我必須撤資
I have to take it out.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不行
You can't.
丹尼  我們的對沖基金有三個月的鎖定期
Danny, our hedge fund has a three-month lock-in period.
我會付違約金
So I'll pay the penalty.
-你的銀行會因此遭受重創  -有多少
- You'd take a beating. - Well, how much is it?
原始投資的70%
70% of your original investment.
70%
70%?
抱歉  伙計
Look, I'm sorry, man.
我想幫你  但我無能為力
I'd love to help you, but there's nothing I can do.
周末見  好嗎
I'll see you this weekend. Okay?
不  求你
No, please!
不  不  不
No, don't! Don't! No! No!
不
No! No!